...we set aside a day to celebrate
all your contributions to my life...
(Sheldon:)...both actual and imagined by you.
(Sheldon:)We could call it Leonard's Day.
I kind of Iike the sound of that.
(Sheldon:)Of course you do.
It's about you, like everything else.
(Sheldon:)Oh, thank goodness. I don't think I had it
in me to make another glass of water.
(Leonard:)So do I get breakfast in bed
on Leonard's Day?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Can I sit in your spot?
- Could I control the thermostat?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Do I get a card?
(Sheldon:)Of course you get a card.
(Sheldon:)It's Leonard's Day.
(Penny:)Hey, guys. The building manager said
the reason the power went out...
...is someone went into the basement
and pulled the main breaker switch.
(Sheldon:)Really.
(Leonard:)Who do you think did that, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I don't know.